export const chapter = "Chapter - 19: Spelling and Formation of Words ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "How can a new word be formed from a verb to a noun?",
          optionA: "By adding a prefix",
          optionB: "By changing parts of speech",
          optionC: "By making a compound word",
          correctAnswer: "B) By changing parts of speech",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is an example of forming a new word by adding a suffix?",
          optionA: "leakage",
          optionB: "armchair",
          optionC: "impure",
          correctAnswer: "A) leakage",
        },
        {
          question: "What method is used to create the word 'shoemaker'?",
          optionA: "Adding a prefix",
          optionB: "Making a compound word",
          optionC: "Adding a suffix",
          correctAnswer: "B) Making a compound word",
        },
        {
          question: "What does the idiom 'to beat about the bush' mean?",
          optionA: "To increase existing excitement",
          optionB: "To find something extremely funny",
          optionC:
            "To talk about something for long without coming to the main point",
          correctAnswer:
            "C) To talk about something for long without coming to the main point",
        },
        {
          question: "In the phrase 'to carry the day,' what does it imply?",
          optionA: "To express openly",
          optionB: "To contend successfully",
          optionC: "To be successful",
          correctAnswer: "C) To be successful",
        },
        {
          question: "Which idiom means 'to find fault'?",
          optionA: "to die laughing",
          optionB: "to pick a hole in a man's coat",
          optionC: "to laugh in one's sleeves",
          correctAnswer: "B) to pick a hole in a man's coat",
        },
        {
          question: "How is the word 'immaterial' formed?",
          optionA: "By adding a prefix",
          optionB: "By changing parts of speech",
          optionC: "By adding a suffix",
          correctAnswer: "A) By adding a prefix",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is NOT an example of forming a compound word?",
          optionA: "armchair",
          optionB: "breakfast",
          optionC: "impure",
          correctAnswer: "C) impure",
        },
        {
          question: "What method is used to create the word 'patriotism'?",
          optionA: "By adding a suffix",
          optionB: "By adding a prefix",
          optionC: "By changing parts of speech",
          correctAnswer: "A) By adding a suffix",
        },
        {
          question: "Which idiom means 'to laugh secretly'?",
          optionA: "to die laughing",
          optionB: "to laugh in one's sleeves",
          optionC: "to give vent to",
          correctAnswer: "B) to laugh in one's sleeves",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "We can form a new word by changing parts of speech, for example, from verbs to nouns like 'accompany' to _______.",
          optionA: "company",
          optionB: "accompany",
          optionC: "accompanies",
          correctAnswer: "A) company",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Another way to form a new word is by adding a ______ to it, which is added at the beginning of a word.",
          optionA: "prefix",
          optionB: "suffix",
          optionC: "compound",
          correctAnswer: "A) prefix",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The word 'shoemaker' is an example of forming a new word by making a ______ word.",
          optionA: "prefix",
          optionB: "suffix",
          optionC: "compound",
          correctAnswer: "C) compound",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The idiom 'to laugh in one's sleeves' means to laugh ______.",
          optionA: "openly",
          optionB: "secretly",
          optionC: "loudly",
          correctAnswer: "B) secretly",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the phrase 'to carry the day,' what does it imply? It implies ______.",
          optionA: "success",
          optionB: "competition",
          optionC: "failure",
          correctAnswer: "A) success",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which method is used to create the word 'immaterial'? By adding a ______.",
          optionA: "prefix",
          optionB: "suffix",
          optionC: "compound",
          correctAnswer: "A) prefix",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The word 'leakage' is formed by adding a ______ to the word 'leak'.",
          optionA: "prefix",
          optionB: "suffix",
          optionC: "compound",
          correctAnswer: "B) suffix",
        },
        {
          question: "Plantation farming is primarily found in ______ regions.",
          optionA: "temperate",
          optionB: "tropical",
          optionC: "arid",
          correctAnswer: "B) tropical",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Rubber is primarily produced from the rubber tree in ______ according to the text.",
          optionA: "India and Brazil",
          optionB: "China and the US",
          optionC: "Indonesia and Sri Lanka",
          correctAnswer: "C) Indonesia and Sri Lanka",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Commercial grain farming, mixed farming, and plantation farming are the main types of ______ mentioned in the text.",
          optionA: "subsistence farming",
          optionB: "commercial farming",
          optionC: "intensive farming",
          correctAnswer: "B) commercial farming",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "A new word can be formed by changing parts of speech.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Adding a prefix to a word can form a new word.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Compound words are formed by joining two words.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The idiom 'to laugh in one's sleeves' means to laugh openly.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "The phrase 'to carry the day' implies failure.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adding a suffix is a method to create a new word.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Plantation farming is primarily found in arid regions.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Rubber is primarily produced from the rubber tree in India and Brazil.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Intensive farming is one of the main types of farming mentioned in the text.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Commercial farming involves growing crops for personal consumption within the family and community.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
